const queryList = [
  {
    question: "Who can participate? 🌐",
    answer:
      "DUHacks 3.0 is open to a diverse range of participants, including students, professionals, and individuals with varying skill levels. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced developer, despite the field of academic discipline chosen, you are eligible to join us! 🚀",
  },
  {
    question: "What if this is my first hackathon?",
    answer:
      "Congratulations on considering your first hackathon! DUHacks 3.0 is a great opportunity for beginners. We would be having expert sessions, guidance by mentors along the way to help you out in executing your ideas into projects. See you in the hackathon! 🤖",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Do I need to pay a registration fee to participate in the hackathon?",
    answer:
      "No. There is no registration fee for participating in the hackathon. This approach ensures that creativity and innovation can flourish without restrictions, allowing participants to immerse themselves in a collaborative and dynamic environment.🌐✨",
  },
  {
    question:
      "As the hackathon is in hybrid mode, who is allowed to participate in offline mode?",
    answer:
      "Only selected students from DDU are permitted for offline participation. Participants from any other locations are not allowed.🚫",
  },
  {
    question:
      "For the participants in offline mode, will travel reimbursement be provided?",
    answer:
      "No, DUHacks 3.0 does not offer travel reimbursement for participants in offline mode. Participants are responsible for their travel expenses, and we recommend planning accordingly.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Will everyone from DDU be eligible for offline tickets, or is there a selection process?",
    answer:
      "Not everyone from DDU will receive offline tickets for DUHacks3.O. The selection process involves a shortlisting of participants based on specific criteria, such as performance, engagement, and commitment. Eligible individuals will be notified in advance.😊",
  },
  {
    question: "What should be the team size?",
    answer:
      "The team size can range from a minimum of 1 participant to a maximum of 4 participants. 🤝",
  },
  {
    question: "Are team members from other colleges allowed?",
    answer:
      "Yes, DUHacks 3.0 welcomes participants from diverse backgrounds, including those from different colleges. The hackathon encourages collaboration and networking among individuals with varied experiences and expertise. 🌍",
  },
  {
    question: "What will I get after attending DUHacks 3.0? 🏆",
    answer:
      "DUHacks 3.0 offers a dynamic platform for learning and collaboration. Engage in workshops, network with industry professionals, and develop hands-on projects. Gain exposure to cutting-edge technologies, enhance problem-solving skills, and compete for prizes. Elevate your resume, build lasting connections, and join a vibrant community of innovators in this national-level hackathon. 🚀",
  },
  {
    question: "What if I do not have a team?🤔",
    answer:
      "We have a great community on Discord. Reach out to other innovators, collaborate, communicate, and make things possible! 🤝",
  },
  {
    question: "Have more questions? 🤔",
    answer:
      "Feel free to write to us at gdsc@ddu.ac.in or create a ticket🎫 on discord",
  },
];

export default queryList;
